{
    "id": "61d55e779856419f913747f4c648c751",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He stayed here for ……………………… days.",
            "description": "A few refers to a small number. Few means almost none.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71a5e45ef3b54da3b900ea1e0cbf5411"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is taller than ………………………… of his four brothers.",
            "description": "We use all to talk about more than two.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2933603171e54c8b945ecbddf7771999"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindi is …………………….. difficult than Chinese.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e058f2f8569e48348ab3184caeb87da6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam is ……………………. than Mary.",
            "description": "Elder and eldest can only be used before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "older",
                "elder",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff5c029f18b04495a660732273ce98e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ……………………… people who can afford to buy a yacht.",
            "description": "Use many with plural nouns much with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf93c29bdda640e781de3c330e09e594"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… money was wasted on the project.",
            "description": "Use much before an uncountable noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3cae11f6fd074082a0290112cda1c141"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………… book on World War II.",
            "description": "Use the with superlative adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9fa06eeeace44eabfc830a33e702b60"
        },
        {
            "question": "A donkey is …………………………. than a horse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "usefuller",
                "more useful",
                "useful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "390f919ef3174a1a845f10e50ac9b442"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer tea ……………………… coffee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "347b311bb0a04b37a42eaaf3ed7f831b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………of the two.",
            "description": "We use the comparative form to talk of two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "the cleverer",
                "the cleverest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "329a18cfa7a74511ae01f55641a3ee69"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have never seen …………………….. a good boy.",
            "description": "Such is used before a noun or adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72a45eb855d14bf99a25606e6d31974f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children performed really …………………………",
            "description": "Well is an adverb and good is an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e6da07472534d4d9bcece60a7d7e2e6"
        }
    ]
}